http://www.wiredzune.com/privacy-policy/

Your Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following urlhttp://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, WiredZune.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.
Collection of Personal Information
When visiting WiredZune.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links to third party Websites
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.
Advertisers
Advertise Here!
Pages
About
About Zune
Contacts
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
Zune Products
Categories
Apple (5)
Microsoft (13)
Wired Zune Exclusive (4)
Wired Zune News (71)
Zune 2 (3)
Zune Accessories (11)
Zune Articles (131)
Zune Capabilities (2)
Zune Competitors (2)
Zune Connected (6)
Zune Deals (3)
Zune Phone (4)
Zune Social (1)
Zune Software (9)
Zune Specs (1)
Zune's New Looks (7)
Partners
iPod to Computer
Privacy Software
Tivo
PLR Articles
iPod Touch
Zune Software
Zunerama
Subscribe
Zune Friends
ClicZune
Music Zune (DE)
Zune MAX
Zune Thoughts
Got Zune?
Become One!
Career Spotlight
One of the most saught after careers these days is that of a certified nursing assistant or CNA. They provide care for the injured, disabled and mentally ill typically in nursing homes and hospitals. You can learn more at the cna training guide.
Archive
May 2010
August 2009
June 2009
May 2009
November 2008
October 2008
September 2008
© Copyright 2006 - 2007 Wired Zune.
Theme by Lionel.
Entries (RSS)
and Comments (RSS).
WiredZune.com is in no way affiliated with Microsoft. All content rights reserved unless stated otherwise.
